This is a tool for chinese learners.
Mnemo:
Grep =, tags, empty (eg.meng4 dream)

Img:
Input, output
I m sure  you 

This system has spared me many hours of studying.
It is much more fun just to read wuxia / comics / whatever instead of just memorizing vocabulary.

*No need to be online
It can be used offline.

*Mobile devices
Generated output can be read on mobile devices (symbian, java (all you need is a html reader), including eReaders (kindle, etc.). See how to use @on mobile devices and readers@.

*Tags feature
You can add custom tags to the resulting output.
If you are using a @#mnemonic@ system, you can display your custom tags immediately. See @screenshots@. 
I have put @my personal mnemonics@ online, if you care. 

*Customizable input
You can customize the output in any way you like - by the usage of @templates@. (can be easily used to produce pdf, fb2, xml or anything you might want. Please share interesting usage cases or new formats with others on the @forum@.

*Free
The software is published under GNU3 license.
If you like it, please @#support the development@.
==
I suggest using Anki with Mandarintoolkit plugin. I use a simple script to export the mnemonics from Anki to the pinyin tools.
==
I am a loyal follower of the system described in the book Learning Chinese Characters by Matthews (you can read first 60 pages online for free). After I learned the 800 characters from the book (that took me about 2 months), I started making up my own. The stories I wrote were for my personal use, I did not write them to publish them inthe first place. Consequently, a lot of them might make little sense to you. (Also note I am not a native speaker of English, sorry about any language-related errors.)

But from what I remember, I would be happy to find such a collection at the beginning (at least as inspiration).

You can also check out other such attempts:
Hesig
(by buying the books over these links you support the further development of the software. Thanks!)
...
Taglich Chinesisch (in German, for traditional characters, can be run offline)

=== screenshots ===
The characters marked green are those with no tags yet created (i.e. not yet learned, assuming you set up tags for every known character).

== Feedback ==
Is it
too complicated to use?
too slow?
Would you like some new features?
Does it work on your mobile device?
Do you know any other dictionaries that should be supported?
Please let me know!

=== Propagation ===
Post on cn. forum
Free download sites
Powered by Java
Request permission from taglich
Notice CEDICT usage
Post usage video on youtube
